axs.com.sg 2017-09-09

# AXS Consumer

Privacy Policy   

Last modified: 5 June 2013 

AXS Pte Ltd ("AXS") is a solution provider and operator of an Electronic Service Delivery Network ("ESDN"). AXS operates the AXS network ("AXS Network"), comprising of the AXS mobile application ("AXS Mobile Application"), the AXS website at (the "AXS Website") and the AXS physical self-service kiosks (the "AXS Stations"). 

AXS offers you an alternate electronic channel where you can perform bill payment transactions over the Internet or using our physical AXS kiosks. With new electronic channels you will be able to make bill payments at your convenience. 

AXS respects every individual's right to privacy. Whether you are an AXS customer, a registered user or visitor, we understand the importance you place on the privacy and security of information that personally identifies you or your account information. We refer to and treat this information as "personal information." AXS is committed to protecting your personal information. We are open about our personal information and data collection practices. 

Unless restricted by applicable law, you agree that any and all personal information relating to you collected by AXS from time to time may be used and disclosed for such purposes and to such persons as set out in this Privacy Policy. 

While AXS has put in place the necessary security practices and measures to safeguard against these risks, AXS is still unable to guarantee the complete security of your transactions against any attacks from malicious programmes. 

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on the AXS Website. However, an individual notice will not be sent to you. You will be deemed to have acknowledged and agreed to the amended Privacy Policy if you continue to use the AXS Network after the changes have taken effect. You are reminded to check for updates to this Privacy Policy prior to using the AXS Network. 

If you have any queries, please contact our Data Privacy Officer at dpo@axs.com.sg. 

1\. COLLECTION AND USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

1.1 We do not sell personal information to anyone. 

1.2 You may generally access the AXS Network (including the AXS Website) without the need to give us any of your personal information. 

1.3 We may collect information when you browse the AXS Website. Such information includes without limitation: 

  * Search queries;
  * Internet protocol addresses; and
  * Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

1.4 We collect personal information when you register an account with AXS Plus such as: 

  * Name;
  * Contact number; and
  * Identification number.

1.5 We collect personal information that you provide to us when you contact AXS for recruitment and related purposes. Such personal information are collected, used, and disclosed by AXS in accordance with AXS Personal Data Protection Policy for Job Applicants, a copy of which is published at here. 

1.6 If you choose not to provide the above mentioned personal information, you are still allowed to generally access the AXS Network and access and use the services and content available on the AXS Network. 

1.7 If you contact AXS, we may keep a record of your communication to help to resolve any issues that you may be facing. 

1.8 All personal information and other information collected may be used by AXS in the aggregate or individually and may be combined with other information for purposes including but not limited to the following: 

  * Responding to and taking follow-up action on complaints;
  * Performing office administrative matters;
  * Seeking feedback and comments on AXS's business and operational matters;
  * Marketing the activities, events and services of AXS and its business partners;
  * Providing you with updates on AXS; 
  * Providing you with services that you have requested for (e.g. the AXS Plus service); and
  * Purposes relating to any of the above.

1.9 AXS corporate policies stipulate that any employee with access to confidential customer information is not permitted to use or disclose such information except for business purposes. All employees are required to safeguard such information as specified in their confidentiality agreements with AXS. 

1.10 AXS may need to provide your information to its business partners, legal advisors and service providers. In all cases, your personal information is protected by a strict confidentiality agreement. We have arrangements in place to ensure your personal information is not retained by AXS's business partners, legal advisors and service providers for longer than is necessary for the purpose of providing you with the product, service or information you request. 

2\. DISCLAIMERS

2.1 Through the services and content on the AXS Network, you may be introduced to a variety of third parties. The privacy policies of these third parties are not under AXS's control and may differ from AXS's and you should read the privacy policies of these third parties carefully. The use of any information that you may provide to any third party, or the use of "cookie" technology by any third party, will be governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the third party website that you are visiting. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information that you are providing on such third party website, you should contact the third party website directly for more information and review their privacy policy. AXS shall not be responsible for the actions of such third parties in any manner whatsoever, including but not limited to any violation of such privacy policies or otherwise. 

3\. ACCESS TO AND CORRECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

3.1 Our Data Privacy Officer is responsible for ensuring that requests for access to information and correction of information are properly dealt with in accordance with the procedures described here. 

3.2 All requests for information or requests for the correction of information held by AXS shall be made by completing AXS's standard Request For Information / Correction Form (PDF available here ), and sending a copy of the duly completed form to AXS via email at: dpo@axs.com.sg, or post or fax at: 

AXS Pte Ltd   
61 Mohamed Sultan Road  
Sultan Link #01-11  
Singapore 239001  
Attention: Data Privacy Officer   
Fax: 6636 4550 Telephone: 6389 7979

3.3 Please note that AXS will only accept and act on requests in the English language that comply with this Privacy Policy, and with the applicable charge(s) paid. AXS shall be entitled to reject any request that does not comply with the above. 

3.4 AXS may refuse to disclose or amend any information for the reasons set out in the Personal Data Protection Act 2012. 

3.5 As far as reasonably possible, AXS will respond to your request within thirty (30) days from the date of receipt of the request. If that is not possible, you will be so notified within thirty (30) days from the date of receipt of the request. 

3.6 A fee may be imposed on each request for information. This fee is payable to AXS by way of a cheque made out to AXS Pte. Ltd., and may be subject to revision by AXS from time to time. AXS is not obliged to respond to requests for information that are not accompanied with payment of any applicable fee(s). 

3.7 You understand that when a request to correct information provided by you for the purpose of performing a bill payment transaction is made, AXS may in certain circumstances determine that the nature of the request is to obtain a refund from the transaction, in which case, AXS may require you to file a request for a refund of payments made instead. 

4\. SAFEGUARDING YOUR ACCESS

4.1 At AXS, we are committed to protecting the security and confidentiality of your information so as to provide you with a safe and secure online environment. Our website uses commercially proven security hardware and software products. These security products include routers, firewalls, intrusion detection systems and secure operating system to safeguard your interest. 

4.2 Industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) communication protocol is the de facto cryptographic standard that we use for securing data communication between the browser and the AXS Website. Digital certificate technology is used to ensure transaction privacy, message integrity and server-side authentication. 

4.3 AXS's channel is regularly reviewed and audited by external and internal auditors to ensure that your interest is safeguarded. 

4.4 Apart from the security measures put in place, you play an equally important role in ensuring your online security and account information is not compromised. 

4.5 You should adopt the following recommended practices in protecting the security of your system: 

  * Do not share your account information with anyone.
  * Do not display your account information in a manner that is visible to others and your PC should never be left unattended. For your protection, the web application will automatically terminate your session if there is no activity for a period of time.
  * Always use the recommended browser. All browsers and application software should be upgraded to support SSL 256-bit encryption.
  * Always check that the website address changes from http:// to https:// and a security icon, usually in the form of a lock or key, appears when authentication and encryption is expected.

5\. MISCELLANEOUS

5.1 Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy, AXS may release your personal information when it believes that such release is necessary to: 

  * Comply with any applicable laws;
  * Enforce terms of any agreement between you and AXS; and
  * Protect the rights, property and safety of AXS, other users of the AXS Network, or any other party.
